Run Home.java file from the OptimizationFramework project
User can select different NFRs from the list.
Click on "Proceed Button" to navigate to "Priority Section" screen
Select different NFRs and assign priorities
Click on "Confirm Button" every time to record these priorities
Click on "Generate Solution" to get all possible solutions
Different solutions are listed here.
Click on "Reduce Solution Space" button to navigate to next screen.
In this screen User can assign values for W1 and W2 and Threshold
Click on "Reduce Space" button to view graphical interpretation of the solution space
The first highlighted plot contains all possible solutions
Now the second highlighted plot contains reduced solution space.
Now individual optimized solution can be plotted seperately from this screen
User has to select each of the solution from drop down menu and click on "Plot" button
It will show the highlighted solution in the plot.
Thank you for your patience.